{
    "subject": "resource/The_Bronze_Buckaroo",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Bronze Buckaroo is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9783049821853638,
            "question": "Is The Bronze Buckaroo a movie genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9232628345489502,
            "question": "Who might have directed a film called The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9057134985923767,
            "question": "What might be some popular elements in a film titled The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.878990888595581,
            "question": "What could be the main plot points of a film called The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445327877998352,
            "question": "What kind of work is The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8296604752540588,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a film similar to The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7858052253723145,
            "question": "What era of filmmaking do you think The Bronze Buckaroo represents?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7760536670684814,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in films like The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5300532579421997,
            "question": "Where would you typically find information about The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3787328004837036,
            "question": "How would you describe the potential target audience for The Bronze Buckaroo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Bronze Buckaroo is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7200_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you typically find information about The Bronze Buckaroo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7200_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes found in films like The Bronze Buckaroo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7200_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What era of filmmaking do you think The Bronze Buckaroo represents?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7200_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7200_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can provide the following response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents contain information about The Bronze Buckaroo being classified as a \"Feature Film\" and having a specific genre (Western; Drama). Therefore, the statement \"The Bronze Buckaroo is a type of film\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly describe \"The Bronze Buckaroo\" as a feature film, supporting the statement that it is a type of film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}